This protrusion and degenerated
Arthritis have been smoking for a long time. What is the state of your heart? My heart is
Yearning more. I'm crawling like a baby to know Jesus to love Jesus and
how to have a free spirit
knowing Jesus
Are you free now?
Yes that is it state of your I'm free. What on this issue of the husband you carry?
We divorced that's what I'm saying. Yes
This is second disappointment
Help. What is the state of your heart? You say? I love Jesus. This is how you people like again Jesus
What is the state of your heart?
Don't say you party you never let it go
Because of the sickness dosti cause you unforgiveness
Forgive me tanner will not let you sleep you would not be able to sleep unless you take a drug
look after my sister faced with the we with beautiful fail you think is which is happy which is not a big I
Confirm the Word of God
That's why I brought her from London. It has been a war the glory be to God that is the real thing
She take medicine every three three hours
But it is
create
happiness
Great joy, this is the life everyone need today. My sister. He alone is lonely and attaced cause depression
suicide thought
I'm so angry and
I'm looking after my kids by myself
And there's no support in Islam because this anger that if it's not for my kids, I don't know what I'm gonna do
Let's say that no you are fishing
Just covering so that I can be happy to show that I'm is for me. Otherwise, I'm breaking down pieces
physic
Physically, my body is just torn apart into pieces
My heart I'm having palpitations I cut it like any time now
I don't know this form you feel on internet
This is spiritual ease. Okay, that is contacting you
Oh, very time. What is like a you have withdraw is it it's not a pastor. It's not a man ago
Gradually about to join the courts
Don't touch me
Who brought me I destroy everything
Everything marriage a new relationship every mother come up. I know Maria she is my wife
She is my wife I am dead
She will sleep and get up from my sleep. I want to look for secret I
Introduce it to her through an example
From a baby a baby one day
Dedicated not to me. Do you know how beautiful?
trees
and shit drop
Winds greatest wings I give up. She cannot do anything. No man will stay with her hatred hatred hatred
Destruction in our life in the mighty name of shake
Look
This is the problem the people are facing today
Okay, look at this case of this one mother
You want to pray? Are you pray for this woman without custody demo in her?
The challenges she has will come back to you. Just under your free
Jesus has won the battle and she is free
My name is Ella
Wamba, I'm from Zambia. I live in the UK my
Testimony goes like this. I came from the UK with unable to walk. I had a disc protrusion since
2006 that would like they diagnosed me from then they've been offering me
surgery, and I've been
Refusing as you can see I've got something in my hand is just to you
It might look little but it's very very very very very strong. I've been on this medication since
2006 - now
This one is the Hydra chording 30 milligram. I
Take forth
C to four times a day
Which is very very strong. It just suppresses the pain and this this other one is pre goblin
also
100 and 100 milligram when I take it. I become very drowsy and sleepy
That's work. This has affected me severely that I end up doing two days. I'm a nurse by profession
I work in theatres and in all theatres, you know, you are on your feet all the time
It's a it's just um, I'm a I'm a pen to my work colleague
I'm a pen that I can't go to work because I'm always calling in sick
You know, and I can't sit at home because I become very frustrated very angry. Very lonely. I have to go to work
So a few years a few years now. I've been searching searching with
Settle with the doctors. What is the solution? What is the solution the solution is for me to our surgery
I said no. I cannot have surgery there must be something else
Well a la miss Mamba you just have to stay on a medication before my deliverance
I was addicted. This is an opioid medication
I was addicted to this medicine if I don't take my body, I become agitated. I become you know, it's caused. It's
Up here is a code cocaine. So you become itchy like a druggie my feet
I'm on my back to go down to put my to
To even tie my my slippers. I have to sit down to cream my body
I have to sit and do half of the body up
The second part has been going on for a long time for a while now and as a mother I have two strong boys
As they're growing and you know, they're Nigerian. They're like the I ever asked you I know cannot soup. Mommy you're coming
I want to eat my food my stew. I'm tired from work. Mommy
We need your, you know, you're a best cook I have to start and there are my children. I have to cook for them
So from work, I was done and I'll be telling I said, you know sleeping's they know it's okay
Don't worry just stand there. Take your time. I'll cook. I will finish my midnight
I'll cook a lot and I just live it for them. So that's the effect
It has done in my life, you know
Everywhere I go, you know, imagine a them
You can see I'm sitting on the bus when the plane comes I'll just take this thing
Pop it in my hand and people looking at me, you know, I feel embarrassed
Johnny stop I have to take you for me to be
Sustainable to work from here today. I have to find some way and sit down I move on to God be the glory
the god of TB Joshua I
Don't even know what to say because that is
So
How we got here is the grace of God as you watch the clip. You saw that my
Affliction of sickness was to do with a demonic attack because that's one of the reason I came for
Spiritual husband this has affected me tremendously
I was married perfectly for many years and then all of a sudden it took over marriage destroyed
destroyed beyond recognition
second relationship as you can see man of God prophesied twice within seconds of true relationship the second relationship that I
Was engaged to I just I don't I walked away
obviously the demon doesn't want the same for me to settle down and I
have been I've been aware of my
affliction of the
Spiritual husband and did the dragon because I have been to so many
churches and I mean so many churches both big and small and little five three four ten people thousands and I've had
Encounters of men of God one-to-one like this and that demon will be speaking to me that look at him
Is it the one that's gonna do?
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
You know
It'd be telling me and for real
That demon the man I will have everything manifest everything after four
Then I get up the demonic state and said, you know, I'm still here. I'm not going, you know, and I start crying, you know
I'll go to the next one
They'll say oh there's another one go to this church God that there's a great man of God our God
I want one point in 2012
I had an encounter where a man of God impacted on me and I freaked out that's the spirit of anger
very very severe two
Bounces one on each side grabbed me me. I destroyed I pulled him down
I pulled two bounces on the ground you see how he was manifested that ancient dragon strong dragon
So myself. I was out of the body. I don't know how to explain it
So when I came round to it, I was all bruised and my friend said Jimmy. Do you know what you did?
I said No, what did I do? Say?
Do you know those two boys those two have two men you put them down. I say me
No, you say yes, you put you you were so angry that you had a drag on this thought that I said
Oh, okay. Now I started understanding myself
everywhere I go I'm seeking for solution because
Anger hatred
Poverty I'm a nurse for crying out loud. I am struggling for money. You understand when man of God preached that is covered
Oh, look at his beautiful, man. I don't want to not because of shame, but I'm
Protecting myself. I feel like I am being I
need to protect myself then maybe I don't want to be
missing
People to see me to feel sorry for me John. I don't if I'm making sense praise the Lord and
It's afflicted me so much so much
I've been the church's I've been to that every single one of them until that Sunday
that demo was
Subdued this is my reminder
Shameful, but I'm
glad and I'm grateful to God that I
Have been delivered this thing. You see like this. I cannot do without it
Even in my sleep the deep day. I will be sleeping. I would dream of
Smoking I was see cigarette like this. I was smoke from no way out 2 a.m. Or 3 a.m. Or 5 a.m
I'll just jump out of my bed put on my pajamas and a gun is to him
Nobody's gonna see Miss England and I walk to the cross of the across the road by my secrets
I start walking smoke one or two paths to cigarettes before I know I feel better and now asleep I
Cannot I was smoked this is very expensive now
I
can to to like now I can finish this pack if I'm ready to smoke if I went out sit down there and smoke the
whole pack, I don't know what
It's just something we're just telling me smoke and I don't smoke like, you know
The whales some people who smoke inhale come through the nose. I don't know how to do
I'll just be our puffy and I'll throw it
I'll take another one puffy our throats and then from there I'm thinking I'm plotting something is telling me
ok, you can do this and you do that some
Not anything good
It says its voice
Physically, it destroys your body. You know, it's a cancerous
Toxic toxic smoke in your body and I don't see it that way, you know, it's it allowed it caused me to start having palpitations
you know because I
Am you know from nowhere, I woke upmy. I'm having chest pains. I'm having because I'm thinking I'm smoking. I'm thinking of other things and
It's just
This really affected me so bad. I've been doing it for the past. I was the same time. I started having pain since 2012
So 2012. I started smoking praise the Lord in some most most cases like okay
I'm seeking solution if I want to do something, let's say okay. I know my problem
I've discovered that I have a spiritual husband. I'm gonna go to church to this church and there's a man of God day
I was sit down in a congregation and I will see the man of God
Somehow my body will shift and the thing will be communicating when a man of God gets closer
There will be communicating that do you think you and the money man of God is actually literally staring at Memphis
He's not saying anything. He's looking at me
And the thing is that Damon is speaking to him said you cannot deliver me. I am here to stay me
I will disgrace you and the manner what who just passed me. I'll just go what happened to me the man of God permittivity
I shall approach to you my case. I know is different. Everybody is different because I've been encouraged for
watching the clips of how
Other women or men who are delivered from spiritual husband's what I was expecting is not what happened that day
Man of God was coming
If you watch this clip of that someone that day it wasn't going that way kept on coming to that corner
Caps on facing me me and him had an encounter
nobody knew I saw him if he was a clip it he kept on doing that is and he's walking away to my
Direction that was the time. I was before anybody realized I was subdued I was weak before I even came to spoke to me
I couldn't and there was no communication between me and him. It did not allow it to speak to him
So he walks away and he says are you free free more of me. Take more of me
Give me more of you and he's walking away kept on coming back and he worked on his to death and he was looking at
me but he was preaching but I
Connected with him, and now my spirit being was gone was weak and I took over and I started feeling something
emotional and then when he approached me to speak stop prophesying towards me as you can see my deliverance was I
Started crying, you know when people say that they experience
Electric shock this that that my one is I said, I just broke down
Inside and outside. I was just crying crying crying. It's
emotional deliverance
You see what I said Elian from the time it was preaching and it did as he's working
It went like towards my corner and when like he's you know when he's doing be gone
And I know he was speaking to me because I was that demon was subdued
That from from then on when he came in I couldn't hear anything. There was no community today
I haven't had any voice to tell me anything
To speak to me that I'm here. Oh, you know I feel
Okay, I feel free. I feel empty and I was hungry after okay now de palma de mallorca came to anyway. Tell us what happened
As he was speaking you have a look of a meme my
so me my brokenness know my sickness is know my
My affliction of anger of the
Demon, that was done to me and my whole life. I'm a nice person, you know, but when I get angry, I
I am I'm not a nice person to be around and I must make sure that I have the last say
That's why I used to do and it's not nice
it's not nice to do to people I
Work it affected me outward that oh, they know me is Elodie Eva?
that's my name at work because I'm a diva I must make
points
It's not nice to be known like that
Okay, we know you have lots to say based on your past experiences or to God be the glory
It's written of the past now
Could you just tell us the money Monica came to you?
We give you messages of prophecy written laws exactly what Monica said about you how you can confirm this to be true
As they was approaching me with my deliverance taking place in started a prophesy word
for things he said my
my relationship
You know is because of this this this situation is because of your relationship your anger your you are keep it's in there
That's why you are sick, and I just I started breaking down
my heart started breaking down and I was crying and then
You know, I started mentioning about my desire
I was second disappointment, which is true because I'm divorced the first one and the second piece of audio harvest
This is the second disappointment. Yes. It's true because my
Fiance is the disappointment. I broke it off
No him breaking it off. I broke it off
We cannot understand but only me understand and I confirmed that to be true and then he went on to
Prophesy that oh, I have I did
Internet forum. Um, I should it was it will I thought it was a man of God
But it wasn't a man of God and if I had filled in the form I would have been
into a coach
which is a confirmed to be true because a week before I came she doesn't even know that I didn't tell her my workplace a
patient
Had somebody I met her there was sitting there waiting for the family member
they sat down with the Bible and it which is read in the
Hospitals in England and they was talking and he's talking with the children's children about the Bible became intrigued us
You know, what are you doing?
You know and then he said oh, yeah, we do Bible study online
If I if you're interested, I'll take your number then we do
I will send you an application
Form you fill it in and when you fill it in I'll send it back to you to you and I'll be sending you Bible
quote so that you can do Bible study and I confirm it to be true because that's the only thing I can remember that I
would have done
With that prophecy. It's 100% true. And then the Fed the fourth one was about the depths
Big depth, I am in big big depth that when the prophecies
Also two hundred percent true praise the Lord man. Thank you very much
And now let's come straight to your experience the woman the man of God touched you what happened?
When the man who got the first when as he was approaching me
I was as you can see the video I'll just weak I was weak and then the first touch I had the strong
energy energy
of
anointing that
subdued the end of the
demon beside be that was behind and from then on I
Could not remember anything all I saw myself. I was just crying and I woke up crying
That's all I could remember praise the Lord in mind. Well
Immediately. I felt the back pain that feel I feel it just
Went off I just liked my back just felt so light
You know, I didn't feel their heaviness. I went offense I went on my knees
It's like I couldn't wait to come on my knees. I just went straight down onto my knees. I
The things I cannot do I just started immediately. You can see the clip
I just feel free to
To stretch my leg and you know that I've been running out in my room without
Realizing I run this like three I have two stairs
I'll run up the stairs and and I asked one of their coordinator say did I just do that?
She said yes, you just did that, you know, which I could not do before
I am free in Jesus name okay to really confirm what you're talking about Regis the most reasonable things
you couldn't do because of that terrible sickness that was caused by the
demonic dragon that was possessing you then just the most seasoned with music and delight not I couldn't do then I
Could not I have to hurt somebody before I knew down I have to hurt somebody but now I could just freely
And then you know before I could call it take me away
I wouldn't even dare attempt to go on my knees and get to nap. I just get up by myself and
you know, I've been sitting on the chair for hours and hours and hours and
I'm not feeling heavy on my back. You know, I'm just I just feel free my feet. I just
light shower Klopfer wonderful Jesus Christ
Since my deliverance, I haven't had any voices, so I'm here
it's like I'm
Not I'm missing something. You know, I've had in the past all those like somebody's walking behind me
I'm always looking behind but I haven't felt. I feel empty you understand
I feel free and this the the craving for cigarettes. I just look at it. I'm not feeling it. I have not felt
the
Craving for smoking what you want to do with this now?
Once what I want to do with them, I have to get rid get rid of it
We'll get rid of it all of them
Get rid of it get rid of it. I'm free for medication because I am not addicted to any man any
Medication and cigarettes in Jesus name don't ever ever if you encounter
Emanuele TV with the whole team at
One point don't ever ask anybody for an opinion that do you what do you think about that church?
When you encounter a manual TV by yourself follow your what God is telling you and find your way here praise the Lord
Emmanuel Emmanuel
God is really with us indeed. The way I find her is through God's grace
my name is auj asanga I
Mean I Geryon they are living UK praise the Lord
I used to be a nurse by retired now. I'm a retired person
yeah when I met her I
Told her that the only way out is Jesus
But remember she was a Christian there
so as a Emmanuel television, that's
founded by myself
nobody introduced me to
synagogue Church of All Nations
Because when I came home one time, I wanted to come here, but what I had scared me out
Then one day I saw a magazine
written about
TB Joshua
Apik Europe are ready three days
Then I became convinced within my heart that this is a prophet of our generation if you check
If you check your Bible the final in every generation does a profit and
I give God the glory that I'm part of it man. I've been part of it for a long time
But in secrets, yeah
So I thank all so much
The way he brought us here was a miracle when we came here starting from the airport. That was a problem. She fell down
That to coast we were at a party 1:00 a.m. So we couldn't come straight before the morning we came here
We were received like we are princess like we are invited. That's why what we are told
The Torah all sort of team that will suit us, but we were received
Then on Sunday
It happened. The deliverance came
The war I can tell the world is that I've been watching hands is a deliverance
Normally we use the locker or for migraine. She never heard my grave. Well most to Weezer
no time of a period ruled us another war a
Happily here our our next-door bed did not know what happened a semi an huh
And I've seen a lot of changes in half
So that gives me joy the advice I have for the whole world and people looking at me here
Please please read only church deceive you
When she will deliver here, the church was attending sent a clich
Immediately. I see her to leave that place she sing and go somewhere for deliverance
We are still in the church. I said but we are all of us are children of God
They supposed to be happy for her being delivered. So this energy should go to one city
I don't know where it is in LA in Legos here. So my advice to the world some of you are sick
You say don't want to be showing television you are dying come here. It's a freedom place a place of Liberty